<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>[DCS] Addons (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.DCSAddons</packageId>
  <author>CaptainSnafu</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/DCSAddons</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>Mlie.DeadCanServe</packageId>
      <displayName>Dead Can Serve (Continued)</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2548091455</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/emipa606/DeadCanServe/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>Mlie.DeadCanServe</li>
    <li>Haplo.Miscellaneous.Robots</li>
    <li>kamikoto00.Rimofmadness.Vampires</li>
    <li>battlemage64.MoreLances</li>
    <li>Ogliss.Dalrae.BloodPack</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of CaptainSnafus addons for Dead Can Serve 
https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=1776527348

Instead of separate mods I bundled them together. It will load each addon depending on what of the mentioned mods are active.

[list]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=724602224]Misc. Robots[/url]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2369553686]Rim of Madness - Vampires[/url]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1378849687]More Lances[/url]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2192662471]Blood Pack[/url]
[/list]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/DCSAddons][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/Be8E2qJ.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
[h1][DCS] DI Robot[/h1]
DI for Dead Intelligence
In my mod [Dead Can Serve],you can scan the memories from brains in corpses and use them as AI.
In Haplo's mod [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=724602224][Misc. Robots][/url],you can buy independent and movable robots to free your pawns from cleaning and hauling.
And with this mod, you can use MemoryDisk to build the Robots!! No need to wait for the trader and craft whenever and how many you want !!
Of course, you need to unlock the research "Intelligent Servers" in [Dead Can Serve] techtree. Recipes are in the Fabrication Bench.

[h1][DCS]Feed the Vampire[/h1]
This Mod add recipes which allow you turn [BloodBag] from my mod [Dead Can Serve] into [blood pack (lowblood)] from Jecrell's mod [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2369553686][Rim of Madness - Vampires][/url].
So yes, with this Submod, now you can feed your Vampires with the blood from Corpses.
You can find the recipes in Stove or DrugLab.
"A decent vampire will not take someone else's first-aid medicine for a drink.If you want to invite them to drink from the blood bag,at least first remove the medical label on the bag.Anyway,it won't taste well because it's only from the corpse."

[h1][DCS]Dead Can Tame[/h1]
In my mod [Dead Can Serve],you can scan the memories from corpses and make them to psychic lances.
In mod [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=1378849687][More Lances][/url],you can buy more kinds of psychic lance.
And with this mod, you can use Memory Disk to make and upgrade some of these Lances.
1.Can upgrade tamming lance to higher level (from small to medium to all)
2.Can upgarde Psychic Shock Lance to KnockOut Lance
3.Can turn Psychic Soothe Pulser to Brainwash Lance
So yes, you can use dead people's memories to tame any living creatures or cool them down(...by knock them out)
of course, you need to finish the research Psychic Interference or Memory Modification in Dead Can Serve mod.

[h1][DCS]Transfusion from Corpses[/h1]
In my mod [Dead Can Serve],you can draw blood from the corpses and simply use [blood bag] as medicine.
In Dalrae's mod [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2192662471][Blood Pack][/url], you can draw blood from the living people and use [blood pack] to do blood transfusion to cure blood loss.
In this mod, you can turn my [blood bag] to [blood pack].
So, yes, it means you can also do blood transfusion from corpse.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]

</description>
</ModMetaData>